Muhammed Batuhan Aydın

+90 (551) 262 35 05 · info@batuhanaydn.com · @batuhanaydn Elazığ /TURKEY

CYBER SECURITY MEMBER

Muhammed Batuhan Aydın is a software developer and cybersecurity expert with experience in penetration testing, secure network architecture, and software development support. He has given lectures on cybersecurity to children and organized international CTF competitions. Batuhan has detailed knowledge of vulnerabilities and protection methods in the OWASP WEP/API TOP 10 list, and stays up-to-date on newly discovered vulnerabilities and attack and defense techniques. He is experienced in team management, cohesion, and project development and implementation, making him a valuable asset to any organization.

KEY COMPETENCIES

I have detailed and applied knowledge OWASP WEP/API Top 10 vulnerability list Java, PHP, Laravel, Bash and Python working experience Team leadership Communication Project management

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

OWASP Foundation Organizer & Leader

Sep 2022 - Present

Accomplishments:

- By organizing 3 international CTF competitions, I hosted hundreds of CTF players and prepared the event questions.
- I gave conferences to children who are interested in cyber security throughout the province.

Asis Elektronik ve Bilişim Sistemleri A.Ş Cyber Security Consultant

Feb 2023 - Jun 2023

Accomplishments:

- I conducted penetration tests at regular intervals for many transportation services in 36 provinces.
- Supported teams in Firewall configurations, Secure network architecture and software development.

Efol A.Ş Software Developer Team Leader

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

Accomplishments:

- I managed a 12 person developer team within the company.
- Me aim was to improve the virtual payment solutions in all dealers within our company by developing an easy payment software we named Efolpay.
- I prepared EfolB2B and a rent a car B2B system, making it accessible and usable by the company's internal staff.
- I strengthened the defense of the company's core resources by providing cybersecurity awareness trainings to the company's over 200 personnel.
- I conducted audits of security devices on company servers and wrote reports about them.

PROJECT AND COMPETITIONS

Owasp Foundation Capture The Flag (CTF) - Organizer

Sep 2022

- There was a sweet competition in the online, 60-question CTF competition I organized at https://ctf.owasp.org.tr/.
- A total of 100+ teams participated in the competition throughout the competition.
- The questions consisted of questions such as web security, mobile security, network security in terms
 of difficulty and structure.

Havelsan Havelsan - Hackathon On The Train

May 2022

- Application Havelsan server management software, Port MYS, is an extension written in Laravel. Our goal was to win the competition by creating innovative ideas for this application.
- We designed a mobile app using Telegram technologies for the remote control of the Port MYS application.
- In this way, we provided 100% remote access to the servers by adding another server and a telegram service to the server side.
- · Our project was selected as the second best project

Vodafone Vodafone Red Hackathon - Vodafone Guvendeyim

Mar 2022

- It was developed as a Vodafone Hackathon project and came 2nd in the competition.
- It is a software developed for locating citizens who do not have internet at the time of earthquake. It works on the principle of integrating radio relays into base stations.
- Technology was used by Vodafone during the painful earthquake we experienced.

NASA Space Apps Challenge - Project ISS

May 2022

- NASA Space App was developed for the hackathon competition and came in 3rd place in the competition.
- It aims to protect the International Space Station from space debris. For this, emergency protocols were developed and simulated.

EDUCATION

Firat University

Computer Engineering Undergraduate Student, third year